<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>foss on BiRabittoh</title><link>https://birabittoh.github.io/tags/foss/</link><description>Recent content in foss on BiRabittoh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 16:58:16 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://birabittoh.github.io/tags/foss/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Modernizing XFCE</title><link>https://birabittoh.github.io/articles/void-xfce/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 16:58:16 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://birabittoh.github.io/articles/void-xfce/</guid><description>This article is more of a memo for myself. Since I often re-install Linux systems, I spend a lot of time doing repetitive tasks and often forget some steps, which leads me to waste even more time figuring out what&amp;rsquo;s wrong.
These instructions allow you to get a fully functional and modern-looking XFCE desktop on a fresh install of Void Linux (even though they can be adapted to work in any distro).</description></item><item><title>Update your mirrors!</title><link>https://birabittoh.github.io/articles/reflector/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 12:48:40 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://birabittoh.github.io/articles/reflector/</guid><description>Nah, I&amp;rsquo;m not talking about bluetooth mirrors. Mirrors are what powers all distros: they&amp;rsquo;re a (de)centralized solution for downloading pre-compiled binaries and scripts for your operating system.
Suspicion I like always having the most current version of packages, so I usually update my system several times a day. When, after a day, I ran sudo pacman -Syu and it reported the system being up to date, I was pretty weirded out.</description></item><item><title>Data volatility</title><link>https://birabittoh.github.io/articles/data-volatility/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 10:31:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://birabittoh.github.io/articles/data-volatility/</guid><description>I tried to access my domain at smol.pub yesterday and I noticed the service went down. Fear started rushing through my veins as I noticed I would have to choose another platform and, most importantly, write everything back from scratch since I don&amp;rsquo;t have a backup. This made me think about the importance of always having a backup stored somewhere.
Why though Creating a backup of your important data is crucial.</description></item><item><title>You should probably use Linux</title><link>https://birabittoh.github.io/articles/you-should-use-linux/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://birabittoh.github.io/articles/you-should-use-linux/</guid><description>Why are you writing this? As you probably know, I like using free software (free as in freedom, not free of charge). Most people see users with this mentality as a group of paranoid psychopaths who circlejerk about their custom systems. While that&amp;rsquo;s in part true, there&amp;rsquo;s much more to it.
I often get asked by Windows or MacOS users about why they should think about switching to a GNU/Linux OS (which I&amp;rsquo;ll be referring to as Linux); I&amp;rsquo;m just going to address everything here so I don&amp;rsquo;t have to repeat it to everyone who asks.</description></item><item><title>Modern web bloat</title><link>https://birabittoh.github.io/articles/modern-web-bloat/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://birabittoh.github.io/articles/modern-web-bloat/</guid><description>This is it. My first blog post; I suppose this officially makes be a boomer.
Inspiration Some time ago I stumbled upon a video, where the popular Linux influencer Luke Smith talked about the effort of looking up a Chicken Parmesan recipe in 2021 without having any adblock or privacy extensions enabled.
That&amp;rsquo;s because most modern websites take a lot of time to load framework files, ads and trackers. While that&amp;rsquo;s kinda functional, I think we should change our habits and start making simple websites again.</description></item></channel></rss>