<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on BiRabittoh</title><link>https://bi-rabittoh.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on BiRabittoh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© BiRabittoh</copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 21:50:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bi-rabittoh.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The AI takeover is near?</title><link>https://bi-rabittoh.github.io/posts/ai-art-contest/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 21:50:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bi-rabittoh.github.io/posts/ai-art-contest/</guid><description>Context August 29, 2022. The Colorado State Fair gives out prizes for various art categories in a contest. Let&amp;rsquo;s have a look at Théâtre D&amp;rsquo;opéra Spatial, the winner for category no.5: Digital Arts / Digitally-Manipulated Photography (leaderboard).
That same day, a heated debate started on Twitter (as if that weren&amp;rsquo;t the norm there). That&amp;rsquo;s because the winner of this art contest used Midjourney, a popular AI image generator, to generate their entry.</description></item><item><title>My opinion on FOMO</title><link>https://bi-rabittoh.github.io/posts/fomo/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 11:21:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bi-rabittoh.github.io/posts/fomo/</guid><description>What are you even talking about Let me preface this by saying I know nothing about psychology and behavioral studies, so anything you read here is just my personal opinion.
Let&amp;rsquo;s start with defining FOMO, to make sure we&amp;rsquo;re all on the same spectrum.
Fear of missing out (FOMO) is the feeling of apprehension that one is either not in the know or missing out on information, events, experiences, or life decisions that could make one&amp;rsquo;s life better.</description></item><item><title>GGVG01 - Fran Bow</title><link>https://bi-rabittoh.github.io/posts/ggvg01/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 11:29:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bi-rabittoh.github.io/posts/ggvg01/</guid><description>While I&amp;rsquo;m a free software enthusiast, I love videogames as an art form (even if playing them involves messing with ugly DRM). That&amp;rsquo;s why I&amp;rsquo;ve decided I will start talking (spoiler-free) about my favorite ones in my new series: the Geminaut&amp;rsquo;s Guide to Video Games!
Context Fran Bow was developed by Killmonday Games, a Swedish indie studio composed of Natalia and Isak Martinsson. This game was suggested to me by my ex-girlfriend.</description></item><item><title>Data Volatility</title><link>https://bi-rabittoh.github.io/posts/data-volatility/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 10:31:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bi-rabittoh.github.io/posts/data-volatility/</guid><description>I tried to access my domain at smol.pub yesterday and I noticed the service went down. Fear started rushing through my veins as I noticed I would have to choose another platform and, most importantly, write everything back from scratch since I don&amp;rsquo;t have a backup. This made me think about the importance of always having a backup stored somewhere.
Why though Creating a backup of your important data is crucial.</description></item><item><title>You should probably use Linux</title><link>https://bi-rabittoh.github.io/posts/you-should-use-linux/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bi-rabittoh.github.io/posts/you-should-use-linux/</guid><description>Why are you writing this? As you probably know, I like using free software (free as in freedom, not free of charge). Most people see users with this mentality as a group of paranoid psychopaths who circlejerk about their custom systems. While that&amp;rsquo;s in part true, there&amp;rsquo;s much more to it.
I often get asked by Windows or MacOS users about why they should think about switching to a GNU/Linux OS (which I&amp;rsquo;ll be referring to as Linux); I&amp;rsquo;m just going to address everything here so I don&amp;rsquo;t have to repeat it to everyone who asks.</description></item><item><title>Modern Web Bloat</title><link>https://bi-rabittoh.github.io/posts/modern-web-bloat/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bi-rabittoh.github.io/posts/modern-web-bloat/</guid><description>This is it. My first blog post; I suppose this officially makes be a boomer.
Inspiration Some time ago I stumbled upon a video, where the popular Linux influencer Luke Smith talked about the effort of looking up a Chicken Parmesan recipe in 2021 without having any adblock or privacy extensions enabled.
That&amp;rsquo;s because most modern websites take a lot of time to load framework files, ads and trackers. While that&amp;rsquo;s kinda functional, I think we should change our habits and start making simple websites again.</description></item></channel></rss>